自计算黎明以来，编码一直
Coding has been the bread and butter for
是开发人员的面包和黄油。
developers since the dawn of computing.
我们习惯于通过将需求分解为可组合
We're used to creating applications by breaking down
的问题来创建应用程序，然后
requirements into composable problems
可以对其进行编码。
that can then be coded against.
因此，例如，如果我们
So for example, if we have to write
必须编写一个算出库存分析的应用程序，
an application that figures out a stock analytic,
也许价格除以比率，
maybe the price divided by the ratio,
我们通常可以编写代码
we can usually write code to get
以从数据源中获取
the values from a data source,
值，进行计算，然后返回结果。
do the calculation and then return the result.
或者，如果我们正在写
Or if we're writing a game
游戏，我们通常可以弄清楚规则。
we can usually figure out the rules.
例如，如果球撞
For example, if the ball hits
到砖块，则砖应该
the brick then the brick should
消失，球应反弹。
vanish and the ball should rebound.
但是，如果球从屏幕的底部
But if the ball falls off the bottom of
掉下来，那么球员也许会失去生命。
the screen then maybe the player loses their life.
我们可以使用此图表示。
We can represent that with this diagram.
规则和数据出现答案。
Rules and data go in answers come out.
规则以编程语言
Rules are expressed in
表示，数据可以来自
a programming language and data can come from
从本地变量一直
a variety of sources from
到数据库的各种来源。
local variables all the way up to databases.
机器学习重新排列了这个图表，
Machine learning rearranges this diagram
我们将答案放入数据
where we put answers in data
中，然后将规则删除。
in and then we get rules out.
因此，我们不是作为开发人员
So instead of us as developers figuring
弄清楚何时应删除砖块的规则，
out the rules when should the brick be removed,
玩家的生命终止或
when should the player's life end,
对任何其他概念的所需分析是什么，
or what's the desired analytic for any other concept,
我们将要做的就是为我们
what we will do is we can get a bunch of
想要的东西得到很多
examples for what we want to
示例查看然后让计算机找出规则。
see and then have the computer figure out the rules.
现在，这对于无法通过自己弄清楚
Now, this is particularly valuable for problems that
规则来解决的问题特别有价值。
you can't solve by figuring the rules out for yourself.
因此，请考虑这个示例，活动识别。
So consider this example, activity recognition.
如果我正在构建一个设备，该设备可以
If I'm building a device that detects if somebody is say
检测到有人说走路并且有关于
walking and I have data about their speed,
他们的速度的数据，
I might write code like this
我可能会编写这样的
and if they're running well that's
代码，如果它们运行良好，
a faster speed so I could adapt my code
这是一个更快的速度
to this and if they're biking,
骑自行车，那还不错。
well that's not too bad either.
我可以这样调整代码。
I can adapt my code like this.
但是后来我也必须做高尔夫的认可，
But then I have to do golf recognition too,
现在我的概念被打破了。
now my concept becomes broken.
但是，不仅如此，
But not only that,
当然，仅凭速度就可以做到很幼稚。
doing it by speed alone of course is quite naive.
我们以不同的速度行走和跑步，
We walk and run at different speeds uphill and
下坡和其他人
downhill and other people
以不同的速度行走和跑步。
walk and run at different speeds to us.
因此，让我们回到此图。
So, let's go back to this diagram.
最终，机器学习非常
Ultimately machine learning is very
相似，但我们只是翻转轴。
similar but we're just flipping the axes.
因此，我不得不妥协，而不是
So instead of me trying to express the problem as
我试图将问题作为规则
rules when often that isn't even possible,
表达为规则。
I'll have to compromise.
新的范式是我得到了
The new paradigm is that I get
很多示例，然后在这些示例上
lots and lots of examples and then I have
有标签，我使用数据说
labels on those examples and I use
这就是步行的样子，这就是跑步的
the data to say this is what walking looks like,
样子，这就是自行车的
this is what running looks like,
样子，是的，是的，是的。
this is what biking looks like and yes,
即使这也是高尔夫的样子。
even this is what golfing looks like.
因此，随着计算机推断
So, then it becomes answers and data
规则，它成为答案和数据。
in with rules being inferred by the machine.
然后，机器学习
A machine learning algorithm then
算法可以计算每组数据
figures out the specific patterns in
集中确定
each set of data that
每个数据的特定模式。
determines the distinctiveness of each.
这就是这个编程范式
That's what's so powerful and
如此强大和令人兴奋的原因。
exciting about this programming paradigm.
这不仅仅是做同样
It's more than just a new way
旧事物的新方法。
of doing the same old thing.
它打开了以前无法
It opens up new possibilities
做到的新可能性。
that were infeasible to do before.
因此，在接下来的
So in the next few minutes,
几分钟中，我将向您展示创建
I'm going to show you the basics of creating
神经网络的基础知识，
a neural network which is
这是进行这种模式识别的主力。
the workhorse of doing this type of pattern recognition.
神经网络
A neural network is
只是机器学习的更先进的实现，
just a slightly more advanced implementation of
我们将其称为深度学习。
machine learning and we call that deep learning.
但是幸运的是，编码实际上非常容易。
But fortunately it's actually very easy to code.
因此，我们将直接进入深度学习。
So, we're just going to jump straight into deep learning.
我们将从一个简单的开始，然后继续
We'll start with a simple one and then we'll move on
进行大约10行代码
to one that does computer vision
的计算机视觉。
in about 10 lines of code.
但是，让我们从一个非常简单的“ Hello World”示例开始。
But let's start with a very simple "Hello World" example.
因此，您可以看到一切如何悬挂在一起。
So you can see just how everything hangs together.